<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Kent Barrett Art</title>
    <link>https://kentbarr.github.io/KBA/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Kent Barrett Art</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Oct 2015 13:07:31 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://kentbarr.github.io/KBA/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Migrate from Jekyll</title>
      <link>https://kentbarr.github.io/KBA/blog/migrate-from-jekyll/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Oct 2015 13:07:31 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kentbarr.github.io/KBA/blog/migrate-from-jekyll/</guid>
      <description>Move static content to static Jekyll has a rule that any directory not starting with _ will be copied as-is to the _site output. Hugo keeps all static content under static. You should therefore move it all there. With Jekyll, something that looked like
▾ &amp;lt;root&amp;gt;/ ▾ images/ logo.png  should become
▾ &amp;lt;root&amp;gt;/ ▾ static/ ▾ images/ logo.png  Additionally, you&amp;rsquo;ll want any files that should reside at the root (such as CNAME) to be moved to static.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hugo is for lovers</title>
      <link>https://kentbarr.github.io/KBA/blog/hugo-is-for-lovers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Aug 2015 13:39:46 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kentbarr.github.io/KBA/blog/hugo-is-for-lovers/</guid>
      <description>Step 1. Install Hugo Goto hugo releases and download the appropriate version for your os and architecture.
Save it somewhere specific as we will be using it in the next step.
More complete instructions are available at installing hugo
Step 2. Build the Docs Hugo has its own example site which happens to also be the documentation site you are reading right now.
Follow the following steps:
 Clone the hugo repository Go into the repo Run hugo in server mode and build the docs Open your browser to http://localhost:1313  Corresponding pseudo commands:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creating a new theme</title>
      <link>https://kentbarr.github.io/KBA/blog/creating-a-new-theme/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jun 2015 13:50:46 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kentbarr.github.io/KBA/blog/creating-a-new-theme/</guid>
      <description>Introduction This tutorial will show you how to create a simple theme in Hugo. I assume that you are familiar with HTML, the bash command line, and that you are comfortable using Markdown to format content. I&amp;rsquo;ll explain how Hugo uses templates and how you can organize your templates to create a theme. I won&amp;rsquo;t cover using CSS to style your theme.
We&amp;rsquo;ll start with creating a new site with a very basic template.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://kentbarr.github.io/KBA/articles/agency-artificial-persons-for-idiots/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kentbarr.github.io/KBA/articles/agency-artificial-persons-for-idiots/</guid>
      <description>THE TENDER FOR LAW: AGENCY (ARTIFICIAL PERSONS) FOR IDIOTS &amp;copy; 2014 ROGUESUPPORT INC. under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-NoDerivs 3.0 Unported License. HER MAJESTY AND AN ORGANIZATION . It&amp;rsquo;s the ultimate artificial person . To understand what this means you should refer to my earlier articles. The Criminal Code of Canada states, _inter alia_ [Source R.S., c. C-34, s. 2 &amp;ldquo;INTERPRETATION&amp;rdquo; ]:
&amp;rdquo; every one&amp;rdquo;, &amp;rdquo; person&amp;ldquo; and &amp;rdquo; owner&amp;ldquo;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://kentbarr.github.io/KBA/articles/attorney-general-money-by-lou-manotti/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kentbarr.github.io/KBA/articles/attorney-general-money-by-lou-manotti/</guid>
      <description>THE TENDER FOR LAW: ATTORNEY GENERAL MONEY &amp;copy; 2016 ROGUESUPPORT INC. under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-NoDerivs 3.0 Unported License. It was mentioned by a member, that the concept of ATTORNEY GENERAL MONEY was not well known; so this is to clean up any misconceptions and to make a few things clear.
In order for any money to be useful, it must be ACCEPTED by all PARTIES. Since every country that the International Monetary Fund (IMF) touches is in receivership, any money created must comply with the IMF&amp;rsquo;s receivership rules.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://kentbarr.github.io/KBA/articles/childrens-aid-society-for-idiots/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kentbarr.github.io/KBA/articles/childrens-aid-society-for-idiots/</guid>
      <description>THE TENDER FOR LAW – CHILDREN&amp;rsquo;S AID SOCIETY [C.A.S] FOR IDIOTS &amp;copy; 2013 ROGUESUPPORT INC. under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-NoDerivs 3.0 Unport ed License.
This article is what we like to call an &amp;ldquo;emergency article&amp;rdquo; in as much as Dean Clifford has publicly and blatantly lied about family services and the law. Before we get started we are going to refer to the JURISDICTION I am most familiar with. You will find mirrors of this in any JURISDICTION that uses a world reserve currency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://kentbarr.github.io/KBA/articles/corpus-delicti/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kentbarr.github.io/KBA/articles/corpus-delicti/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;CORPUS DELICTI&amp;rdquo; The MOST IGNORED LEGAL CONCEPT! THE TENDER FOR LAW: PERSONS FOR IDIOTS &amp;copy; 2014 ROGUESUPPORT INC. under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-NoDerivs 3.0 Unported License.
The circle-jerkers at Quatloos have been scouring the 1960 CANADIAN BILL OF RIGHTS for what is supposedly my own &amp;ldquo;crazy&amp;rdquo; position that for a CRIME, there must be an INJURED PARTY. They LOVE cherry-picking, or just plain ignoring the maxim of CORPUS DELICTI! Even their precious &amp;ldquo;Justices&amp;rdquo; agree with me!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://kentbarr.github.io/KBA/articles/channeling-nancy-or-why-lying-is-really-bad/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kentbarr.github.io/KBA/articles/channeling-nancy-or-why-lying-is-really-bad/</guid>
      <description>30 May 2015 at 03:45 A Tender For Law Article by Ceit Butler&amp;copy;, under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-NoDerivs 3.0 Unported License.
I am what you would describe as &amp;ldquo;an avid reader&amp;rdquo;. I started young; my grandmother had taught me to read chapter books by the time I turned 3, and in doing so she forever instilled in me a love of reading. I spent the majority of my formative years with my nose buried in a book.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://kentbarr.github.io/KBA/articles/defamatory-libel-for-idiots/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kentbarr.github.io/KBA/articles/defamatory-libel-for-idiots/</guid>
      <description>THE TENDER FOR LAW: DEFAMATORY LIBEL FOR IDIOTS; A Serendipitously, Happily-Coincidental Article &amp;copy; 1982-2015 ROGUESUPPORT INC. under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-NoDerivs 3.0 Unported License.
In case none of you read that LICENSE, that means that no COMMERCE is expected and/or IMPLIED&amp;hellip;again, in case you are confused. Only members of THE TENDER FOR LAW will understand why that&amp;rsquo;s so important. ALSO: there are no &amp;ldquo;answers&amp;rdquo; here, just a &amp;ldquo;setting of the scene&amp;rdquo; as it were&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://kentbarr.github.io/KBA/articles/free-dumb-the-truth-and-robert-menard/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kentbarr.github.io/KBA/articles/free-dumb-the-truth-and-robert-menard/</guid>
      <description>THE TENDER FOR LAW - Pseudo-article-to-tide-you-over-while-we-continue-work on-the-next-article: FREE-DUMB - THE TRUTH &amp;amp; ROBERT MENARD! &amp;hellip;OK, not really. Roll the copyright and licence!
&amp;copy; 2014 ROGUESUPPORT INC. under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-NoDerivs 3.0 Unported License.
( Shut up! It&amp;rsquo;s coming!)
In the super-secret group, THE TENDER FOR LAW (https://www.facebook.com/groups/tenderforlaw/), I was asked a very interesting question regarding how soon one of my &amp;ldquo;predictions&amp;rdquo; will come to pass.
Those that have come to know me recently, and/or those who have known me for a longer period (20 years or more), can all agree on one thing; I see shit coming, and I understand substantially more than everyone else.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://kentbarr.github.io/KBA/articles/give-in-lieu-of-identification/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kentbarr.github.io/KBA/articles/give-in-lieu-of-identification/</guid>
      <description>NOTICE OF WAIVER OF PUBLIC BENEFITS (ONTARIO CHANGE OF NAME ACT [R.S.O. 1990, CHAPTER C.7])
WHEREAS YOU, being a PUBLIC SERVANT and/or an OFFICER for a PUBLIC TRUST, and/or A GOVERNMENT AGENT/OFFICIAL, have demanded &amp;ldquo;IDENTIFICATION&amp;rdquo; from ME, and
WHEREAS YOU, being a PUBLIC SERVANT and/or an OFFICER for a PUBLIC TRUST, and/or A GOVERNMENT AGENT/OFFICIAL, do NOT have the right, and/or AUTHORITY, to attach SURETY and/or JOINDER, to ANY NAME DERIVED FROM A PUBLIC DOCUMENT, and attach such NAME and/or JOINDER to ME, and</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://kentbarr.github.io/KBA/articles/insurance-for-the-inept/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kentbarr.github.io/KBA/articles/insurance-for-the-inept/</guid>
      <description>THE TENDER FOR LAW – APPOINTED ARTICLE - INSURANCE FOR THE INEPT - By APPOINTMENT of Gail Blackman &amp;copy; 2013 ROGUESUPPORT INC. under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-NoDerivs 3.0 Unported License.
One of the great things about being in a law forum, run by a prorogued noble, is that you have the unique opportunity of posing the right question and always getting a near-magical answer; which causes something to flip in that little lump of protoplasm you laughingly call a brain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://kentbarr.github.io/KBA/articles/its-all-natural/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kentbarr.github.io/KBA/articles/its-all-natural/</guid>
      <description>IT&amp;rsquo;S ALL NATURAL! 26 June 2014 at 20:40 You often hear me lament the fact that there are people who only pretend to think. I often counter this unfortunate phenomenon with Tim Minchin&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Storm&amp;rdquo;. More specifically, I reference the quote &amp;ldquo;Do you know what they call alternative medicine that&amp;rsquo;s been proven to work? &amp;hellip;medicine&amp;rdquo;. The alternative medicine crowd has no idea what this means, as they consider PhotoShop pictures and Youtube videos &amp;ldquo;proof&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://kentbarr.github.io/KBA/articles/joinder-for-idiots/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kentbarr.github.io/KBA/articles/joinder-for-idiots/</guid>
      <description>THE TENDER FOR LAW: JOINDER FOR IDIOTS &amp;copy; 2014 ROGUESUPPORT INC. under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-NoDerivs 3.0 Unported License.
Well, spring is here. The days are getting longer, tulips and other spring shit are showing up; I&amp;rsquo;m sure somewhere there are robins and stuff, and the FREE-DUMBERS seem to have bred and left shit-stains all over. It&amp;rsquo;s time to do something about that.Today we are going to discuss the LEGAL NAME, the different case and spelling, and what it REALLY means.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://kentbarr.github.io/KBA/articles/lien-your-name/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kentbarr.github.io/KBA/articles/lien-your-name/</guid>
      <description>THE TENDER FOR LAW – LIEN YOUR NAME &amp;copy; 2015 ROGUESUPPORT INC. under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-NoDerivs 3.0 Unported License.
Appointed by: Dan &amp;ldquo;Lien-Your-Name&amp;rdquo; Wilson
&amp;hellip; that&amp;rsquo;s just a fancy way of saying he asked for it.
I&amp;rsquo;m nearing the end of my run in the public here, so I think I&amp;rsquo;ll stir the financial pot again. Today we&amp;rsquo;re going to talk about liening your name. I&amp;rsquo;ll cover the benefits, the drawbacks, and what you will actually need to do to accomplish this.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://kentbarr.github.io/KBA/articles/lies-and-the-lying-liars-who-lie-about-the-lies-they-tell/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kentbarr.github.io/KBA/articles/lies-and-the-lying-liars-who-lie-about-the-lies-they-tell/</guid>
      <description>THE TENDER FOR LAW: LIES AND THE LYING LIARS WHO LIE ABOUT THE LIES THEY TELL: An Objective and Fair Analysis of the LAW SOCIETY &amp;copy; 2016 ROGUESUPPORT INC. under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-NoDerivs 3.0 Unported License. As of this writing the Roguesupport Initiative, THE TENDER FOR LAW, is 3.75 years old. The project was started on FaceBook for numerous reasons, one of which was that it meets the LEGAL burden of &amp;ldquo;PUBLIC RECORD&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://kentbarr.github.io/KBA/articles/libertarians-and-my-cat/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kentbarr.github.io/KBA/articles/libertarians-and-my-cat/</guid>
      <description>THE TENDER FOR LAW: Libertarians and my cat. &amp;copy; 2015 ROGUESUPPORT INC. under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-NoDerivs 3.0 Unported License.
Figure 1: This is Meko and Trouble. They are cats
Figure 2: This is Larken Rose. He is a Libertarian. He recently said:
&amp;ldquo;There are plenty of different legalese mythology theories which amount to, &amp;ldquo;You accidentally and secretly AGREED and CONSENTED to be ruled by government by&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo; Then they end the statement with &amp;ldquo;calling yourself a &amp;lsquo;citizen&amp;rsquo;&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;using FRN&amp;rsquo;s&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;having a Social Security Number&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;using a bank account&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;spelling your name in all capital letters&amp;rdquo; or they say it&amp;rsquo;s about living here without filing some magic piece of paper or &amp;ldquo;declaring&amp;rdquo; something or other.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://kentbarr.github.io/KBA/articles/my-belief-is-my-conviction/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kentbarr.github.io/KBA/articles/my-belief-is-my-conviction/</guid>
      <description>THE TENDER FOR LAW: &amp;ldquo;MY BELIEF, IS MY CONVICTION&amp;rdquo; &amp;copy; 2014 ROGUESUPPORT INC. under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-NoDerivs 3.0 Unported License.
I was talking to the man who once fleetingly served as helmsman of the Tycho-Brahe (known to the world as &amp;ldquo;The Fender&amp;rdquo;), heady from his pseudo-victory of seeing a legal connection that I didn&amp;rsquo;t. He decided to take a run at my ultimate CONVICTION; ALL belief is EVIL.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://kentbarr.github.io/KBA/articles/notice-of-mistake/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kentbarr.github.io/KBA/articles/notice-of-mistake/</guid>
      <description>&amp;copy; 2014 ROGUESUPPORT INC. under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-NoDerivs 3.0 Unported License.
NOTICE OF MISTAKE - GET THESE TO ME IF I&amp;rsquo;M ARRESTED NOTICE OF MISTAKE
 TAKE NOTICE THAT: In the matter of SURETY for the LEGAL NAME, I believe that there has been a MISTAKE, as the SOLE BENEFICIARY OF A PUBLIC DOCUMENT has been INCORRECTLY IDENTIFIED as an &amp;ldquo;accused&amp;rdquo; and/or a &amp;ldquo;suspect&amp;rdquo;. FORGIVE ME: If I, AND/OR PERSONS AND/OR FRIENDS OF THE COURT AND/OR SUCH OTHER PARTIES ACTING IN MY INTERESTS, have led A COURT and/or STATUTORY BODY and/or A GOVERNMENT SERVICE and/or AGENTS and/or OFFICERS of such bodies, to believe, by responding to &amp;ldquo;You&amp;rdquo;, and/or &amp;ldquo;JOHN SCOTT DUNCAN&amp;rdquo;, and/or SUCH OTHER IDENTIFICATION, such bodies HAVE ADDRESSED ME AS, that I am the PARTY WITH SURETY in this matter, then that would be a MISTAKE, and please forgive me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://kentbarr.github.io/KBA/articles/oh-say-cant-you-see/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kentbarr.github.io/KBA/articles/oh-say-cant-you-see/</guid>
      <description>THE TENDER FOR LAW: &amp;ldquo;OH, SAY CAN&amp;rsquo;T YOU SEE? - A Primer on Citizenship&amp;rdquo; &amp;copy; 2014 ROGUESUPPORT INC. under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-NoDerivs 3.0 Unported License.
In one of our many lively discussions, on the many lively forums that my captains and I chat in and/or frequent, the erstwhile Captain Wentz revealed a small but interesting factoid that surprised a few people; He pointed out that from 1992 to 2002, he was in fact, the Admiral of the AQUILAE Navy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://kentbarr.github.io/KBA/articles/omnijurisdictional-notice/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kentbarr.github.io/KBA/articles/omnijurisdictional-notice/</guid>
      <description>THE TENDER FOR LAW: AN OMNIJURISDICTIONAL NOTICE &amp;copy; 1982-2015 ROGUESUPPORT INC. under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-NoDerivs 3.0 Unported License.
NOTICE: This document will KEEP GROWING. CONTENT ADDED DAILY TO THIS NOTE!
ATTENTION, SIMU-DRONES:
It&amp;rsquo;s 2015. Things are getting darker, but you are getting smarter. You see now, or at least grasp, how to gain wealth and power, but you are at a loss as to what to do with it if you succeed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://kentbarr.github.io/KBA/articles/one-peoples-public-fraud-oppf-part-one/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kentbarr.github.io/KBA/articles/one-peoples-public-fraud-oppf-part-one/</guid>
      <description>ORIGINALLY PUBLISHED on 23 February 2013 · in THE TENDER FOR LAW:ONE PEOPLE&amp;rsquo;S PUBLIC FRAUD (OPPF) Part ONE &amp;copy; 2013 ROGUESUPPORT INC. under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-NoDerivs 3.0 Unported License.
ONE PEOPLE&amp;rsquo;S PUBLIC FRAUD (OPPF) &amp;hellip; You&amp;rsquo;ll notice I didn&amp;rsquo;t use the word TRUST .
Scams like this diminish the word in much the same way GOVERNMENTS have diminished the words &amp;ldquo;human rights&amp;rdquo;. As this is my forum, I think I will prevent the concept of TRUSTS being diminished any further by this scam.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://kentbarr.github.io/KBA/articles/one-peoples-public-fraud-oppf-part-two_-the-ucc-for-idiots/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kentbarr.github.io/KBA/articles/one-peoples-public-fraud-oppf-part-two_-the-ucc-for-idiots/</guid>
      <description>ORIGINALLY PUBLISHED on 24 February 2013 · in THE TENDER FOR LAW: ONE PEOPLE&amp;rsquo;S PUBLIC FRAUD (OPPF) Part TWO: The UCC for Idiots &amp;copy; 2013 ROGUESUPPORT INC. under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-NoDerivs 3.0 Unported License. As promised, I am now going to cover the UNIFORM COMMERCIAL CODE (or UCC, for you idiots who type with your thumbs.)
FUCK! Myths about THIS shit, sure has &amp;ldquo;done the rounds&amp;rdquo;, hasn&amp;rsquo;t it? No more myths have been generated, out of a piece of regulation, than the UNIFORM COMMERCIAL CODE!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://kentbarr.github.io/KBA/articles/one-trillion-dollars/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kentbarr.github.io/KBA/articles/one-trillion-dollars/</guid>
      <description>&amp;copy; 2016 ROGUESUPPORT INC. under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-NoDerivs 3.0 Unported License.
Jan 28th 2016: Scott Duncan shared Jamie Redman&amp;rsquo;s post HEY! Andrew D&amp;rsquo;Spyder-Pig! Looks like those evil Bitcoin folk have &amp;ldquo;thefted&amp;rdquo; a trillion bucks! :D
Imagine that. The awesome Satoshi Nakamoto has engineered something that &amp;ldquo;Stole&amp;rdquo; a trillion dollars, and proved the viability of the Blockchain. The entire future has been re-written, and the technologies that sprung from it, are here to stay.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://kentbarr.github.io/KBA/articles/obiter-dictum/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kentbarr.github.io/KBA/articles/obiter-dictum/</guid>
      <description>THE TENDER FOR LAW: Obiter dictum: MEADS v. MEADS FOR IDIOTS &amp;copy; 2015 ROGUESUPPORT INC. under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-NoDerivs 3.0 Unported License.
It&amp;rsquo;s time to stir the pot - disturb some shit as it were, stoke the fire, prime the forge, enrich uranium in a centrifuge, shit like that. In order to accomplish this noble goal I&amp;rsquo;m going to do something that, on the surface, seems disgusting. I&amp;rsquo;m going to arm the FREE-DUMBERS WITH THE KNOWLEDGE TO CRUSH MEADS V.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://kentbarr.github.io/KBA/articles/proper-notice-for-idiots/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kentbarr.github.io/KBA/articles/proper-notice-for-idiots/</guid>
      <description>THE TENDER FOR LAW – LIVE EXAMPLE #001 – PROPER NOTICE FOR IDIOTS &amp;copy; 2013 ROGUESUPPORT INC. under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-NoDerivs 3.0 Unported License. TONIGHT&amp;rsquo;S TOPIC: PROPER NOTICE
In one of the many ongoing AQUILAE initiatives, I have cause to produce a NOTICE.
Since I&amp;rsquo;m using THE TENDER FOR LAW as a notebook for my students, I figure I might as well &amp;ldquo;kill two birds with one stone&amp;rdquo; by discussing the aspects of NOTICE here, more specifically PROPER NOTICE.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://kentbarr.github.io/KBA/articles/persons-for-idiots/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kentbarr.github.io/KBA/articles/persons-for-idiots/</guid>
      <description>THE TENDER FOR LAW: PERSONS FOR IDIOTS &amp;copy; 2014 ROGUESUPPORT INC. under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-NoDerivs 3.0 Unported License.
The circle-jerkers at Quatloos have been scouring the 1960 CANADIAN BILL OF RIGHTS for what is supposedly my own &amp;ldquo;crazy&amp;rdquo; position that for a CRIME, there must be an INJURED PARTY. They LOVE cherry-picking, or just plain ignoring the maxim of CORPUS DELICTI! Even their precious &amp;ldquo;Justices&amp;rdquo; agree with me!
That&amp;rsquo;s a MAXIM OF LAW, and they are reading the WRONG DOCUMENT, but let&amp;rsquo;s just cover the CASE LAW.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://kentbarr.github.io/KBA/articles/putting-it-all-together/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kentbarr.github.io/KBA/articles/putting-it-all-together/</guid>
      <description>&amp;copy; 2013 ROGUESUPPORT INC. under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-NoDerivs 3.0 Unported License. In THE TENDER FOR LAW
one of its evolved Maxims is that &amp;ldquo;The gold is in the comments&amp;rdquo;. This is true for me too, as it allows me to gauge just how much you are assimilating. Every once in a while though, a &amp;ldquo;gold nugget&amp;rdquo; comes up for me. This is no easy task, and the scarcity of this gold makes it far more valuable to me than it is to you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://kentbarr.github.io/KBA/articles/surety-for-idiots/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kentbarr.github.io/KBA/articles/surety-for-idiots/</guid>
      <description>THE TENDER FOR LAW – SURETY FOR IDIOTS &amp;copy; 2013 ROGUESUPPORT INC. under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-NoDerivs 3.0 Unported License. It&amp;rsquo;s been a while since I&amp;rsquo;ve posted an article, and I&amp;rsquo;ve solidified the &amp;ldquo;For Idiots&amp;rdquo; concept. Let&amp;rsquo;s cover SURETY!
One of the most painful things about being on FaceBook is having to endure the fact that people with chronic Dunning–Kruger effect still think that their ignorance has the same standing as my knowledge; and they will happily state many unkind things regarding my character when I challenge their &amp;ldquo;pulled-out-of-their-ass&amp;rdquo; mythology.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://kentbarr.github.io/KBA/articles/surety-for-idiots_-part-ii-waiving-the-legal-name/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kentbarr.github.io/KBA/articles/surety-for-idiots_-part-ii-waiving-the-legal-name/</guid>
      <description>THE TENDER FOR LAW – SURETY FOR IDIOTS - PART II - WAIVING THE LEGAL NAME &amp;copy; 2013 ROGUESUPPORT INC. under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-NoDerivs 3.0 Unported License.
THE FOLLOWING is an ENHANCED and TENDER FOR LAW ANNOTATED [In Square Brackets] version of section 2.1 of The ONTARIO &amp;ldquo;Change of Name Act&amp;rdquo; [R.S.O. 1990, CHAPTER C.7&amp;hellip; see what I did there? PAY ATTENTION TO CAPS HERE, as these are the words to look for where YOUR &amp;ldquo;change of name act&amp;rdquo; is.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://kentbarr.github.io/KBA/articles/the-tender-for-law_-the-looming-threat-of-freedumb-addendum/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kentbarr.github.io/KBA/articles/the-tender-for-law_-the-looming-threat-of-freedumb-addendum/</guid>
      <description>THE TENDER FOR LAW: The Looming Threat of FreeDumb - ADDENDUM &amp;copy; 2014 ROGUESUPPORT INC. under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-NoDerivs 3.0 Unported License. ADDENDUM TO [ https://www.facebook.com/notes/scott-duncan/the-tender-for-law-the-looming-threat-of-freedumb/815869621812845 ]
I received a message from a woman today that filled me with both anger and despair. As you may have guessed, I justifiably hold all of you in the highest contempt. Often I find myself longing for the mindset and ethical structure (or lack thereof) that would allow me to take my many extraordinary abilities, and just kill you all.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://kentbarr.github.io/KBA/articles/the-tender-for-law_-the-looming-threat-of-freedumb/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kentbarr.github.io/KBA/articles/the-tender-for-law_-the-looming-threat-of-freedumb/</guid>
      <description>The Looming Threat of FreeDumb &amp;copy; 2014 ROGUESUPPORT INC. under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-NoDerivs 3.0 Unported License.
In this writing I shall go further into my Noble Title, the Trust I commissioned in 1982, the Constitution, and the term &amp;lsquo;Freeman&amp;rsquo;.
My grandfather (John Clark Duncan) was an extraordinary man. He was of Noble descent, and served the Royal House of Windsor in World War II, training fighter pilots and later joining the 435&amp;frasl;436 Burma Star Squadron; where he was remembered for saving a bunch of people&amp;rsquo;s asses (and giving somebody else the credit), and depth-charging a whale off the coast of Vancouver island.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://kentbarr.github.io/KBA/articles/the-truth-about-the-illuminati-or-why-piece-of-shit-christians-are-such-pieces-of-shit/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kentbarr.github.io/KBA/articles/the-truth-about-the-illuminati-or-why-piece-of-shit-christians-are-such-pieces-of-shit/</guid>
      <description>Shared under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-NoDerivs 3.0 Unported License.
SCOTT DUNCAN·WEDNESDAY, 21 OCTOBER 2015 &amp;rdquo; Piece-of-Shit Christians&amp;rdquo; - you hear me say it a lot. I say it so much, and I&amp;rsquo;ve been saying it for so long, that the prefix &amp;ldquo;Piece-of-Shit&amp;rdquo; is automatically inserted in front of it, each and every time I hear the word &amp;ldquo;Christian&amp;rdquo;. This is much like the experience of Elliot in &amp;ldquo;Mr. Robot&amp;rdquo; with &amp;ldquo;Evil Corp&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://kentbarr.github.io/KBA/articles/whos-on-first_-for-idiots/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kentbarr.github.io/KBA/articles/whos-on-first_-for-idiots/</guid>
      <description>Who&amp;rsquo;s On First: FOR IDIOTS &amp;copy; 2015 ROGUESUPPORT INC. under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-NoDerivs 3.0 Unported License. For anyone still lagging behind in the &amp;ldquo;name game&amp;rdquo; confusion surrounding systems relating to law and money, I present, &amp;ldquo;Who&amp;rsquo;s on First?&amp;rdquo;
Also for your edification, I have copied/pasted the opening sentences from Wikipedia describing the comedy routine, below:
&amp;ldquo;Who&amp;rsquo;s on First?&amp;rdquo; is descended from turn-of-the-century burlesque sketches that used plays on words and names.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://kentbarr.github.io/KBA/articles/you-think-wrong-and-value-the-wrong-things/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kentbarr.github.io/KBA/articles/you-think-wrong-and-value-the-wrong-things/</guid>
      <description>THE TENDER FOR LAW: YOU THINK WRONG AND VALUE THE WRONG THINGS - By Tara Duncan &amp;copy; 2015 ROGUESUPPORT INC. under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-NoDerivs 3.0 Unported License. While this is predominantly directed at personal friends and acquaintances, there are perhaps some FB group members who may benefit from the information in this article, as well. This should not be new information to most. It does seem, however, to be a repeating theme.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://kentbarr.github.io/KBA/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kentbarr.github.io/KBA/contact/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How To Setup Airspace Hugo</title>
      <link>https://kentbarr.github.io/KBA/blog/installation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kentbarr.github.io/KBA/blog/installation/</guid>
      <description>Install this template by following those simple steps: STEP-1 : Hugo installation Check this link below for install hugo on your computer. hugo install documentation
STEP-2 : Create your project Hugo provides a new command to create a new website.
hugo new site &amp;lt;new_project&amp;gt;  STEP-3 : Install the theme Run this command
hugo new site airspace-hugo  and then go to the themes folder inside of airspace-hugo folder. You can also use this command cd airspace-hugo/themes for going to this folder.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Service</title>
      <link>https://kentbarr.github.io/KBA/service/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kentbarr.github.io/KBA/service/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Work</title>
      <link>https://kentbarr.github.io/KBA/work/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kentbarr.github.io/KBA/work/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>